<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Managing Your Account on Manual</title>
    <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Managing Your Account on Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How do I change my settings?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-change-my-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-change-my-settings/</guid>
      <description>You can change your account settings by clicking on your username in the top right corner of the vBulletin site. This will provide a dropdown menu. From here select &#34;User Settings&#34;.
On the settings page, you will see up to five tabs. Profile, Settings, Privacy, Notifications and Subscriptions. These are:
Profile - This is the public information that is shown to everyone. You can control who sees your information on the Privacy tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I change my Avatar?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-change-my-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-change-my-avatar/</guid>
      <description>To add an avatar to your account, please visit your user profile. You can visit your User Profile by clicking on your name in the upper right corner and selecting &#34;User Profile&#34; from the drop down menu.
Once on your user profile, hover your mouse over the default avatar presented. You will be shown a link to upload your avatar. Click on it and follow the instructions on the screen. If you&#39;re avatar is too large, you will be provide with an opportunity to clip the image to fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I customize my profile?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-customize-my-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-customize-my-profile/</guid>
      <description>The site administrator may have given you the ability to customize your profile. This allows you to change the fonts, colors and backgrounds on different elements of your user profile. To get started click on your name in the top right corner and select My Profile from the drop down. Once viewing your User Profile, click the &#34;Customize My Style&#34; button in the left column.
This will open up the customization interface above your user profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I reset my user profile to the default?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-reset-my-user-profile-to-the-default/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-reset-my-user-profile-to-the-default/</guid>
      <description>To revert your customized Profile Style to the default site style, click on your user name in the top right corner of the page. Select My Profile off the dropdown menu.
On your profile screen click &#34;Customize My Style&#34;. This will open the Customization Tools above your profile.
Click the &#34;Default&#34; button and your style should show the default site style again.
To save your changes click the &#34;Save&#34; Button and exit the customization tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I edit my signature?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-edit-my-signature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-edit-my-signature/</guid>
      <description>You can set and change your signature by going to your username in the upper right corner &gt; click to get the drop down &gt; select User Settings. On that page, select the Account tab and then go down to the area that says &#34;Conversation Detail Options&#34;. On the right side, you will see the option &#34;Edit Post Signature&#34;. If you click that link, you will get a popup editor that will allow you to enter/edit your signature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I use images in my signature?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/can-i-use-images-in-my-signature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/can-i-use-images-in-my-signature/</guid>
      <description>It is up to the Administrator whether you may use images in your signature. If you are allowed to attach them, then an Upload Attachments button will be available on the signature editor popup.
updated: 2021-10-06 01:30pm | Version: 5.6.5 Alpha 11 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I manage my privacy?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-manage-my-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-manage-my-privacy/</guid>
      <description>You may manage your privacy settings by going to your username in the upper right corner &gt; click to get the drop down &gt; select User Settings. On that page, select the Privacy tab. On that page you may customize who can see and comment on things you started, replied, followed and following under your profile. You may select to show these things to Everyone (default), your Subscribers, or all Members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I manage my notifications?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-manage-my-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-manage-my-notifications/</guid>
      <description>You may manage your notification settings by going to your username in the upper right corner &gt; click to get the drop down &gt; select User Settings. On that page, select the Notifications tab. One this page, you may select your Email Notifications (turn it on, make it daily or weekly, or choose to get it through the message center only). You may also set what type of Notifications you would like to receive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are Subscribers?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/what-are-subscribers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/what-are-subscribers/</guid>
      <description>Subscribers are users that have subscribed to your profile. You will receive a Notification if someone subscribes to you (user settings -&gt; notifications) and you may choose to Accept or Ignore their request to subscribe to your profile. You may also set it up so that you will automatically accept any subscriber&#39;s request in User Settings &gt; Privacy &gt; Subscriber Request &gt; enter a checkmark next to Auto-accept subscriber requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I ignore another member?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-ignore-another-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/how-do-i-ignore-another-member/</guid>
      <description>If there are particular members that are bothering you and you do not wish to see their posts or receive Private Messages from them, then you can add these members to your &#39;Ignore List&#39;.
In the top right of the forum, click your Username. A dropdown menu will appear and from here you need to select &#39;User Settings&#39;. On the page that appears, click &#39;Account&#39; and scroll to the bottom. In the text area next to &#39;Ignore List&#39;, enter the Usernames of users that you want to Ignore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Private Messages</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/using-private-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/using-private-messages/</guid>
      <description>If the administrator has enabled the Private Messaging system, registered members may send each other private messages to communicate outside of the general forum discussions.
How do I send Private Messages?Private messages work a little like email, but are limited to registered members of this forum. You may be able to include BB code, smilies, images and other attachments in private messages that you send.
You may send a private message to a member of this forum by clicking the &#39;Compose New&#39; button in the top left section of your Message Center, or by clicking the &#39;Private Message&#39; button that is visible on the User Profile of a member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Visitor Messages</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/using-visitor-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/using-visitor-messages/</guid>
      <description>Visitor messages are publicly viewed messages posted on member profile pages. To post a message, navigate to a member&#39;s profile and enter your content using the form at the top of the section. The message you post will be viewable to all visitors of this profile, including but not limited to, guest users and search engine robots if the administrator has allowed this. To communicate privately with a member, send a Private Message instead using the option just above the Visitor Message form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Reputation?</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/what-is-reputation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/end_user_guide/managing_account/what-is-reputation/</guid>
      <description>Reputation is a way of rating users depending on the quality of their posts. If the administrators have enabled reputation, then the like icon will be visible in posts.
You can build your reputation on the site by posting informative and constructive content. This in turn will encourage people to follow your posts, press the like button on different posts and they could even subscribe to your content.
How do I give reputation?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
