<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Styles on vB5 Manual and API Documentation</title>
    <link>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Styles on vB5 Manual and API Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Search In Templates</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/search_templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/search_templates/</guid>
      <description>lets you search for strings in templates from the style(s). Additionally you can run a &amp;ldquo;find and replace&amp;rdquo; search which allows you to replace all instances of a certain string with another string.
This page needs to be created&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replacement Variable Manager</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/replacement_variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/replacement_variables/</guid>
      <description>Replacement variables are useful in representing commonly used values in styles and user content. They allow you to easily replace content items from users and in page text in a finished page output. Use the Styles &amp;amp; Templates &amp;gt; Replacement Variable Manager group to add / modify / delete replacement variables. Note: To learn more about Replacement Variables, please read the Replacement Variables Introduction The Replacement Variable Manager lists all of your styles, together with any replacement variables defined within them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download/Upload Styles</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/download_upload_styles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/download_upload_styles/</guid>
      <description>This section covers how to download and upload styles.
Downloading styles is handy when you want to make a backup of your templates and options, or share your work with other forum administrators.
Uploading styles is handy to revert to a backup or applying the same style to several boards. You can use this option to import a style that someone has given you.
Make sure you read and understand all the options to avoid incomplete style downloads / uploads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Updated Templates</title>
      <link>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/find_updated_templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5manual.test/administration/AdminCP/styles/find_updated_templates/</guid>
      <description>vBulletin&amp;rsquo;s default templates are often updated during upgrades. During this process the system will automatically try to merge any customizations into the new defaults. Should this merge fail, the template will be listed here. As the administrator, you will be able to compare your old version with the new version to make any necessary changes. You can choose to modify or revert a template if it is listed. If you select revert, your customizatized template will be deleted from the system and the default will be used.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
