<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Options on vB5 Manual and API Documentation</title>
    <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Options on vB5 Manual and API Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Turn Your vBulletin On and Off</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/turn-your-vbulletin-on-and-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/turn-your-vbulletin-on-and-off/</guid>
      <description>Site Active From time to time, you may want to turn your site off to the public while you perform maintenance, update versions, etc. When you turn your site off, visitors will receive a message that states that the site is temporarily unavailable. Administrators will still be able to see the site.
Variable Name: bbactive Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Reason For Turning Site Off The text that is presented when the BB is closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Name / Contact Details</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/site-name-contact-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/site-name-contact-details/</guid>
      <description>Forum Name Name of your forum. This appears in the title of every forum page.
Variable Name: bbtitle Data Type: free Default Value: vBulletin Forums Header Logo URL Enter a custom URL to use for the logo image and the home breadcrumb icon.
If you wish to use the root vBulletin page you should leave this option blank.
Variable Name: titleimageurl Data Type: free Default Value: Allow Unregistered Users to use &amp;lsquo;Contact Us&amp;rsquo; If set to yes, you may require guests to pass Human Verification in order to use this form by enabling the option found in the Human Verification Options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Settings</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/general-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/general-settings/</guid>
      <description>Login Credential Type This option lets users log in using only their email, only their username, or both.
Variable Name: logintype Data Type: number Default Value: 1 Use Login &amp;ldquo;Strikes&amp;rdquo; System Setting this to no will disable the system that prevents a user (with a specific IP address) from logging into an account after entering an incorrect password 5 times.
Variable Name: usestrikesystem Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Post Referrer Whitelist For security purposes, vBulletin only allows data to be submitted via post from within the domain the board is installed on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Party Login Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/third-party-login-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/third-party-login-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable Sign-in with Twitter Enabling this option will allow users to connect their vBulletin account with their Twitter account, and use their Twitter credentials to log-in to the forum.
Variable Name: twitterlogin_enabled Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Enable Registration with Twitter Enabling this option will allow users to connect their Twitter account while creating their vB user account. It will also automatically fill the username &amp;amp; email fields with those fetched from their Twitter account, if available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site URLs and Routing</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/site-urls-and-routing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/site-urls-and-routing/</guid>
      <description>vBulletin URL This is the URL, or web address, that users will use in their bookmarks or address bar to access your site.
Note: do not add a trailing slash. (&amp;rsquo;/&#39;)
Variable Name: frontendurl Data Type: free Default Value: Core URL The location of your core directory. This directory contains the vBulletin engine and is not public. Do not update unless directed to by vBulletin Support.
Variable Name: bburl Data Type: free Default Value: http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/privacy-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/privacy-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable Privacy Consent for Guests This will require all users in the selected locations to consent to information tracking in order to use the site. It will log the time the consent was given and the IP address the consent was obtained from. You can edit the available locations here.
If this is enabled, you must specify a Privacy Policy Page in the Privacy Statement URL setting.
Variable Name: enable_privacy_guest Data Type: free Default Value: Enable Privacy Consent for Registered Users This will collect consent for users in the selected locations when they register or the first time they log in (if they are already registered).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/facebook-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/facebook-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable Facebook Platform Enabling this option will allow users to connect their vBulletin account with their Facebook account. This will also populate your site with Open Graph meta data. Note: users must have Javascript enabled and your server must support TLS/SSL communication for this feature to work.
Variable Name: enablefacebookconnect Data Type: boolean Default Value: 0 Facebook Application ID Enter the Application ID for your Application (see the Facebook Developer page for more information).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Settings</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/image-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/image-settings/</guid>
      <description>Image Processing Library Choose the image processing library that vBulletin will use for processing thumbnails and avatars. GD is more widely available but ImageMagick is more robust, supporting more image types. ImageMagick must have a valid path chosen below.
Variable Name: imagetype Data Type: free Default Value: GD ImageMagick Binary Path Path to the ImageMagick 6 binaries (convert and identify). Example:
Unix: /usr/local/bin/
Windows: C:\imagemagick
This option is only used if &amp;ldquo;Image Processing Library&amp;rdquo; is set to &amp;ldquo;ImageMagick 6&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Date and Time Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/date-and-time-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/date-and-time-options/</guid>
      <description>Datestamp Display Option This option controls the display of dates throughout your forum
&amp;lsquo;Normal&amp;rsquo; uses the date and time formats below this option.
&amp;lsquo;Yesterday / Today&amp;rsquo; will show &amp;lsquo;Yesterday&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Today&amp;rsquo; for dates that fall in those periods.
&amp;lsquo;Detailed&amp;rsquo; will show times such as &amp;lsquo;1 Minute Ago&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;1 Hour Ago&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;1 Day Ago&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;1 Week Ago&amp;rsquo;.
Variable Name: yestoday Data Type: number Default Value: 1 Default Time Zone Offset Time zone offset for guests and new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookies and HTTP Header Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/cookies-and-http-header-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/cookies-and-http-header-options/</guid>
      <description>Session Timeout This is the time in seconds that a user must remain inactive before their login session expires. This setting also controls how long a user will remain on Who&amp;rsquo;s Online after their last activity.
Variable Name: cookietimeout Data Type: integer Default Value: 900 GZIP HTML Output Selecting yes will enable vBulletin to GZIP compress the HTML output of pages, thus reducing bandwidth requirements. This will be only used on clients that support it, and are HTTP 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Settings and Optimization Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/server-settings-and-optimization-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/server-settings-and-optimization-options/</guid>
      <description>Cached Posts Lifespan Number of days to maintain a cached copy of a post. This makes topics faster to display, but means that each post takes approximately twice the storage space.
Variable Name: cachemaxage Data Type: number Default Value: 7 *NIX Server Load Limit vBulletin can read the overall load of the server on certain *NIX setups (including Linux).
This allows vBulletin to determine the load on the server and processor, and to turn away further users if the load becomes too high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Style and Language Settings</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/style-language-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/style-language-settings/</guid>
      <description>Default Language Select the default language for your forums. This language will be used for all guests, and any members who have not expressed a language preference in their options.
Variable Name: languageid Data Type: number Default Value: 1 Default Style Select the default style for your forums. This style will be used for all guests, and any members who have not expressed a style preference in their options, or are attempting to use a style that does not exist or is forbidden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Censorship Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/censorship-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/censorship-options/</guid>
      <description>Censorship Enabled You may have certain words censored on your forum. Words you choose to censor will be replaced by the character you specify below. All message titles and messages will be affected.
Variable Name: enablecensor Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Character to Replace Censored Words This character (or characters) will be used to replace censored words. For example, if you have censored the word &amp;lsquo;dog&amp;rsquo; and you set the censor character here to an asterisk () then any occurrences of &amp;lsquo;dog&amp;rsquo; in messages will appear as &amp;lsquo;**&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/email-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/email-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable Email features? Enable the following email-sending features:
Report Bad Post
&amp;lsquo;Contact Us&amp;rsquo; Link
New Post Notifications to Members
Variable Name: enableemail Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Email Flood Check Specify in seconds how much time must elapse before a user may send consecutive emails.
Set to 0 to disable this flood check. Admins are always exempt from this floodcheck.
Variable Name: emailfloodtime Data Type: integer Default Value: 60 Use Cron Based Sending If enabled, vBulletin will send queued e-mails in batches using the scheduled task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Registration Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-registration-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-registration-options/</guid>
      <description>Allow New User Registrations Set this option to NO if you would like to temporarily (or permanently) prevent anyone new from registering. Anyone attempting to register will be told that you are not accepting new registrations at this time.
Variable Name: allowregistration Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Paid Subscription during Registration Allow you to set the paid subscription as a required field during registration that new members need to select a paid subscription and pay before becoming a member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Infractions &amp;amp; Post Reporting Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-infractions-amp-post-reporting-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-infractions-amp-post-reporting-options/</guid>
      <description>Require Infraction Message This option requires that the user sending an infraction include a PM or Email, depending on your forum settings.
Variable Name: uimessage Data Type: number Default Value: 1 Post Reporting Email This option sends an email to the specified users when a post is reported. Users with an active device token will also receive push notifications about the report if Firebase Cloud Messaging is enabled.
Variable Name: rpemail Data Type: number Default Value: 1 updated: 2022-08-29 09:50am | Version: 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Profile Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-profile-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-profile-options/</guid>
      <description>Require Date of Birth Require users to provide a valid date of birth (1902 to current year).
Variable Name: reqbirthday Data Type: boolean Default Value: User Title Maximum Characters This is the maximum number of characters allowed for a user&amp;rsquo;s custom title.
Variable Name: ctMaxChars Data Type: integer Default Value: 25 Censored Words for Usertitle Type all words you want censored in the Usertitle in the field below. Do not use commas to separate words, just use spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Profile: Album Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-profile-album-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-profile-album-options/</guid>
      <description>Albums Per Page When listing multiple albums on one page, this controls how many will be displayed before pagination occurs.
Note: This number must be at least 1.
Variable Name: albums_perpage Data Type: posint Default Value: 10 Pictures Per Page When viewing an album, this controls how many pictures are displayed before pagination occurs.
Note: This number must be at least 1.
Variable Name: album_pictures_perpage Data Type: posint Default Value: 25 Number of Albums to display in the Users Profile The Maximum Number of Albums to Display on the Users&amp;rsquo; Profile Pages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Profile: Style Customization Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-profile-style-customization-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-profile-style-customization-options/</guid>
      <description>Allowed Fonts The list of allowed fonts for profile style customizations. Put each font on its own line.
Variable Name: usercss_allowed_fonts Data Type: free Default Value: arial|Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif times_new_roman|&#39;Times New Roman&#39;, Times, serif courier_new|&#39;Courier New&#39;, Courier, monospace georgia|Georgia, &#39;Times New Roman&#39;, Times, serif verdana|Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif tahoma|Tahoma, Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif geneva|Geneva, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif trebuchet_ms|&#39;Trebuchet MS&#39;, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif comic_sans_ms|&#39;Comic Sans MS&#39;, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif Allowed Font Sizes The list of allowed fonts size for profile style customizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Reputation Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-reputation-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-reputation-options/</guid>
      <description>Default Reputation What reputation level shall new users receive upon registration? Make sure that you have a reputation level that is at least equal to or less than this value.
Variable Name: reputationdefault Data Type: number Default Value: 10 Reputation Undefined If you have any user gain a reputation that exceeds your lowest negative level, then this phrase will be used for them. If you do not wish to use this phrase, make sure you set a negative reputation that is larger than the largest score (negative) that a user on your forum has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Banning Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-banning-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/user-banning-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable Banning Options Banning allows you to stop certain IP addresses and email addresses from registering and posting to the forum.
Variable Name: enablebanning Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Banned IP Addresses Use this option to prevent certain IP addresses from accessing any part of your board.
If you enter a complete IP address (242.21.11.7), only that IP will be banned.
If you enter a partial IP (243.21.11. or 243.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB Code Settings</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/bb-code-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/bb-code-settings/</guid>
      <description>Enabled Built-in BB Code Tags This setting allows you to enable and disable various built-in BB code tags in vBulletin.
Disabling a BB code tag will prevent it from working anywhere on the forum, including signatures, private messages, user notes etc. Disabling Video &amp;amp; Image BB codes will also disable the video &amp;amp; image ckeditor buttons, respectively. Disabling Image BB Code will also disable inline image attachment rendering.
Variable Name: allowedbbcodes Data Type: bitfield Default Value: 59391 Maximum [CODE] Lines When a user posts a block of [CODE], [PHP] or [HTML] in one of their messages, the system will place it in a box, which expands to contain their message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Posting and Editing Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/message-posting-and-editing-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/message-posting-and-editing-options/</guid>
      <description>Multi-Quote Enabled If this option is enabled, an additional button will appear on posts. A user may click as many of these buttons as they wish. Once they click a reply button, the content of each of the selected posts will be quoted and shown in the reply window.
Variable Name: multiquote Data Type: free Default Value: 1 Multi-Quote Quote Limit Enter a value to limit the number of quotes that can be created with Multi-Quote, once this limit is reached the user will be unable to add any more quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachment Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/attachment-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/attachment-options/</guid>
      <description>Image Processing Library Choose the image processing library that vBulletin will use for processing thumbnails and avatars. GD is more widely available but ImageMagick (Imagick) is more robust, supporting more image types. Imagick requires that both Imagick PHP extension and ImageMagick binaries are installed on the server.
Variable Name: imagetype Data Type: free Default Value: GD Enable PDF Thumbnails Using the ImageMagick or Imagick processing library, you can enable thumbnails for PDF attachments if GhostScript is installed on your server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll and Topic Rating Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/poll-and-topic-rating-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/poll-and-topic-rating-options/</guid>
      <description>Maximum Poll Options Maximum number of options a user can select for the poll.
Set this option to 0 to allow any number of options.
Variable Name: maxpolloptions Data Type: integer Default Value: 10 Initial Poll Options The number of options displayed by default when a new poll is created. The actual values displayed will not be less than two or greater than Max Poll Options.
Variable Name: initialpolloptions Data Type: integer Default Value: 3 Poll Option Length Maximum length that a poll option can be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Searching Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/message-searching-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/message-searching-options/</guid>
      <description>Search Engine Enabled Allow searching for posts and topics within the forums. This is a relatively server-intensive process so you may want to disable it if you have problems.
To disable searching of all forums, delete the option from the search_forums template.
Variable Name: enablesearches Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Minimum Time Between Searches The minimum time (in seconds) that must expire before the user can perform a new search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tagging Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/tagging-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/tagging-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable Topic Tagging This is a global option to enable or disable the topic tagging system. You may choose which usergroups can apply tags to topics in the usergroup permissions section.
Variable Name: threadtagging Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Tag Minimum Length The minimum number of characters in a tag name. This can be between 1 and 100.
Variable Name: tagminlen Data Type: integer Default Value: 3 Tag Maximum Length The maximum number of characters in a tag name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Channel Display Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/channel-display-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/channel-display-options/</guid>
      <description>Show Private Forums Select &amp;lsquo;No&amp;rsquo; here will hide private forums from users who are not allowed to access them. Users who do have permission to access them will have to log in before they can see these forums too.
This option applies to any forum listing, including the Quick Navigation menu, and Search Results.
Variable Name: showprivateforums Data Type: free Default Value: 0 Show Topic Prefix in Last Post Column?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topic Display Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/topic-display-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/topic-display-options/</guid>
      <description>User-Settable Maximum Displayed Posts If you would like to allow the user to set their own maximum posts per topic then give the options separated by commas. Example setting: 10,20,30,40
Variable Name: usermaxposts Data Type: free Default Value: 5,10,20,30,40 Show Default Post Icon If you would like to use a default icon for messages without an icon, enter the path to the image here.
Variable Name: showdeficon Data Type: free Default Value: Number of Characters Before Wrapping Text If you want posts to automatically insert spaces into long words to make them wrap after a certain number of characters, set the number of characters in the box above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Messaging and vB Messenger Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/private-messaging-and-vb-messenger-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/private-messaging-and-vb-messenger-options/</guid>
      <description>Private Messaging Enabled Turns the entire private messaging system on and off.
Variable Name: enablepms Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Instant Messaging Support - Check for New Private Messages Selecting &amp;lsquo;Yes&amp;rsquo; for this option will cause the system to check the private message database every time a user loads a page, and will display a visible prompt if a new message has just been saved.
Variable Name: checknewpm Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Maximum Messages Per-Page This setting allows you to limit the number of messages users may display per page on the private messages folder view pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notification Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/notification-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/notification-options/</guid>
      <description>Dismissed Notification Auto Delete Dismissed notifications will automatically be deleted this many days after they have been dismissed. This does not affect new notifications. Set to (0) to disable this functionality.
Variable Name: dismissed_notification_ttl_days Data Type: integer Default Value: 180 New Notification Auto Delete New notifications will automatically be deleted this many days after they were created. This does not affect dismissed notifications. Set to (0) to disable this functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admin Control Panel Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/admin-control-panel-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/admin-control-panel-options/</guid>
      <description>Control Panel Style Folder This setting allows you to specify an alternative style for the Admin / Moderator Control Panels, based on a folder contained within the &amp;lsquo;cpstyles&amp;rsquo; folder. The style you select here will be displayed to all Moderators, and any Administrators who have not expressed their own preference.
Folders in the &amp;lsquo;cpstyles&amp;rsquo; folder must contain at least the following:
controlpanel.css
cp_logo.gif
cp_help.gif
Variable Name: cpstylefolder
Data Type: free</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Data Provider</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/external-data-provider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/external-data-provider/</guid>
      <description>Enable External Javascript This setting allows you to enable/disable the Javascript content syndication system that allows you to embed vBulletin data in HTML pages.
Variable Name: externaljs Data Type: boolean Default Value: Enable RSS Syndication This setting allows you to enable/disable the RSS content syndication system.
Variable Name: externalrss Data Type: boolean Default Value: Enable XML Syndication This setting allows you to enable/disable the XML content syndication system.
Variable Name: externalxml Data Type: boolean Default Value: Topic Cutoff This value controls how many days in the past that updated topics will be chosen from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Error Handling &amp;amp; Logging</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/error-handling-amp-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/error-handling-amp-logging/</guid>
      <description>Log Database Errors to a File If you would like to log all database errors to a file, enter the path to the file here. The file will be saved as {filename}.log.
Errors connecting to the database server will not be logged.
Please note that the directory in which this file is to be created must be writable by the web server.
Variable Name: errorlogdatabase Data Type: free Default Value: Log Failed Admin Control Panel Logins to a File If you would like to log all failed Admin Control Panel login attempts to a file, enter the path to the file here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products/Hook System</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/products-hook-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/products-hook-system/</guid>
      <description>Enable Hook System This setting allows you to globally enable or disable the hook system.
By switching the system off, only vBulletin-native code will be run, so it can be used to establish whether errors exist within vBulletin itself or in hook code.
Variable Name: enablehooks Data Type: boolean Default Value: 1 Add Template Name in HTML Comments Add the template name at the beginning and end of every template rendered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paid Subscriptions</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/paid-subscriptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/paid-subscriptions/</guid>
      <description>Paid Subscription Email Notification An email will be sent to this email address when a paid subscription is purchased or reversed.
Variable Name: paymentemail Data Type: free Default Value: Currency Symbols Enter currency symbols for use with paid subscriptions. Each currency should be on its own line with the currency code followed by the currency symbol separated by the pipe (|). For example &amp;ldquo;usd|US$&amp;rdquo;. Html escape codes can be used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spam Management</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/spam-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/spam-management/</guid>
      <description>Anti-Spam Akismet Service Enables the Akismet service for scanning content posted to the forum. The corresponding API key for the service has to be entered.
Variable Name: vb_antispam_type Data Type: number Default Value: 0 Anti-Spam Akismet Content Key Enter an Akismet service key to enable scanning of user data where supported.
Variable Name: vb_antispam_key Data Type: free Default Value: Stop Forum Spam API Key A Stop Forum Spam API key is required in order to submit spammers to their database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XML Sitemap</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/xml-sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/xml-sitemap/</guid>
      <description>Enable Automatic Sitemap Generation If you select yes for this option, the XML sitemap will be automatically generated periodically by a scheduled task.
Even if you select no, you can still manually generate the sitemap.
Variable Name: sitemap_cron_enable Data Type: boolean Default Value: 0 Automatic Sitemap Generation Frequency (Days) If automatic sitemap generation is enabled, this option controls the number of days between automatic builds.
Variable Name: sitemap_cron_frequency Data Type: integer Default Value: 14 Default Sitemap Priority The default priority for content in the XML Sitemap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vBulletin API and Mobile Application Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/vbulletin-api-and-mobile-application-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/vbulletin-api-and-mobile-application-options/</guid>
      <description>Enable vBulletin API Allow clients to connect to the vBulletin API. Please remember to generate an API key here to allow the API to work.
Variable Name: enableapi Data Type: boolean Default Value: 0 Enable API Log Enables the API log, allowing administrators to track client behavior (or for debuging purposes). Only enable this option if you really need it. The log is stored in the database and can rapidly become large in size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity Stream Options</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/activity-stream-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/activity-stream-options/</guid>
      <description> Oldest Content in Forum This is the oldest post that will be displayed in a forum listing, like the home page.
Variable Name: max_age_channel Data Type: integer Default Value: 60 Maximum Age for Topic This is the oldest post that will be displayed on a standard topic page.
Variable Name: max_age_topic Data Type: integer Default Value: 60 updated: 2022-08-29 09:50am | Version: 5.7.0 Alpha 4 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Tools</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/search-engine-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/search-engine-tools/</guid>
      <description>Enable Google Analytics Enable Google Analytics TrackingYou need to sign up with Google to get your code, and enter the code below
Variable Name: ga_enabled Data Type: boolean Default Value: Google Analytics Javascript Enter Google Analytics code After you have signed up with Google you will get, from their website, an ID and some javascript code. Paste that code into this block to enable Google Analytics for this forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File Scanning</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/file-scanning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/Options/file-scanning/</guid>
      <description>Enabled Scanners At least one scanner must be enabled for vBulletin to scan uploaded files. Note that scanning is performed at the time of upload, and previously uploaded files will not be retroactively scanned after enabling a scanner.
Variable Name: enabled_scanner Data Type: free Default Value: [] Clamd Local Socket Filepath to the unix socket used by the ClamAV Daemon (clamd). Alternatively (if using the TCP socket with clamd) you can use the &amp;ldquo;Clamd TCP Socket IP&amp;rdquo; &amp;amp; &amp;ldquo;Clamd TCP Socket Port&amp;rdquo; options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
