<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Settings on vB5 Manual and API Documentation</title>
    <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Settings on vB5 Manual and API Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Search Type</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/search_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/search_type/</guid>
      <description>This section will show the different search engines installed in vBulletin and allow you to switch between them.
In a new installation of vBulletin 5.0.4 and higher, there two search engines installed. The default is called &amp;ldquo;DB Search&amp;rdquo; and is an indexed implementation stored in a number of tables within your database. This will allow you to search all content types marked as &amp;ldquo;Searchable&amp;rdquo; when they are created/installed in your system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spam Settings</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/spam-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/spam-settings/</guid>
      <description>Anti-Spam Akismet Service Enables the Akismet service for scanning content posted to the forum. The corresponding API key for the service has to be entered.
Variable Name: vb_antispam_type Data Type: number Default Value: 0 Anti-Spam Akismet Content Key Enter an Akismet service key to enable scanning of user data where supported.
Variable Name: vb_antispam_key Data Type: free Default Value: Stop Forum Spam API Key A Stop Forum Spam API key is required in order to submit spammers to their database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Verification Manager</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/human_verification_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/human_verification_manager/</guid>
      <description>Image Image verification presents a series of distorted numbers and letters that the user is required to enter. Either GD2 or ImageMagick support is required from your PHP server in order to use this option. This is the classic option that most users are accustomed to encountering. Disabled users will be blocked with this option.
Question and Answer Question &amp;amp; Answer verification employs a random question challenge with a predefined set of appropriate answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admin Help Manager</title>
      <link>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/admin_help_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vb5support.com/administration/AdminCP/settings/admin_help_manager/</guid>
      <description> Debug Available only in debug mode </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
